Deion, congrats on being drafted. Can
you just take us through maybe the the
waiting game? Like did you expect to get
drafted and what was it like to finally
hear your name called?
Yes, I definitely expected to get
drafted.
However, God makes no mistakes. I'm
where I'm supposed to be and I'm just
excited to get get up there in
Indianapolis and show out. What do you
think you can bring to an NFL team?
Explosiveness,
leadership, work ethic, discipline, man.
I'm a winner, honestly.
I'm explosive. I still believe I'm the
I'm the best in this draft at receiver
and receivers really can't do what I can
do, honestly.
Um
However, man, you're going to get a kid
that's coming in that's ready just to
work.
Kevin. Deion, congrats. Obviously, back
to the state. Can you describe what your
experience was like at Purdue and why
you decided to transfer?
Um yeah, great experience at Purdue.
Like I said, God makes no mistakes. I
was there for a reason as well. I
learned a lot.
However, man, just leaving Purdue, I
just wanted to
get into more complex offense, to be
somewhere where a little bit where they
say competition is at. Um
and that was pretty much the main reason
leaving Purdue, man. Just trying to
expose myself and get around players
with the same mindset like mine.
Nathan, go ahead.
Hey Deion.
What what traits since those days at
Purdue do you feel like you picked up
and what do you bring from an offensive
standpoint to an NFL team like the
Colts?
Um explosiveness,
and being able to win the one-on-one
coverage, man. You're going to get
manned a lot at the next level. I expect
that. However, man, I'm explosive
and I can move great lateral. So,
getting those positions where I'm lined
up one-on-one,
I expect to win my match-up. So, I
definitely feel
explosiveness and
just the ability just to move around in
the slot outside, I can bring that to a
team.
Jake.
Hey Deion. Curious, have you had much
contact with wide receivers coach Reggie
Wayne throughout this process? And
regardless, what what's it like to go
into a program where that's your new
wide receiver coach? Um haven't had that
much communication with him, honestly.
I believe we definitely did talk at
combine.
However, man, I'm excited to get coached
by him, man.
Great receiver coach, man. Got a great
pipeline.
I just can't wait to get up there, man.
If I had to fight tomorrow to get on
there and work, man, I'm ready to work.